1. comment
5. Statement - apkPath = apkName
9. startApplication
13. delay
21. If there is a Update TopuUp, click No, Else you can delay for waiting lazyload
25. Statement - action = new io.appium.java_client.TouchAction(driver)
29. Statement - action.longPress(550, 300).moveTo(100, 300).release().perform()
33. delay
37. Statement - action.longPress(550, 300).moveTo(100, 300).release().perform()
41. delay
45. Statement - action.longPress(550, 300).moveTo(100, 300).release().perform()
49. delay
53. Statement - action.longPress(550, 300).moveTo(100, 300).release().perform()
57. delay
61. waitForElementPresent
65. tap
69. comment
73. comment
79. Wait until Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna Textbox present
85. Verify Element Attribute Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna  with content-desc  to do action
91. SetText to Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna Textbox
97. Hide Keyboard
103. Verify Element Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna which has been you set
109. Wait until Masuk Button  present