1. comment
5. Statement - apkPath = apkName
9. startApplication
13. delay
21. If there is a Update TopuUp, click No, Else you can delay for waiting lazyload
25. Statement - action = new io.appium.java_client.TouchAction(driver)
29. Statement - action.longPress(550, 300).moveTo(100, 300).release().perform()
33. delay
37. Statement - action.longPress(550, 300).moveTo(100, 300).release().perform()
41. delay
45. Statement - action.longPress(550, 300).moveTo(100, 300).release().perform()
49. delay
53. Statement - action.longPress(550, 300).moveTo(100, 300).release().perform()
57. delay
61. waitForElementPresent
65. tap
69. comment
73. comment
79. Wait until Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna Textbox present
85. Verify Element Attribute Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna  with content-desc  to do action
91. SetText to Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna Textbox
97. Hide Keyboard
103. Verify Element Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna which has been you set
109. Wait until Masuk Button  present
115. Verify Element Attribute Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna  with content-desc  to do action
121. Click Masuk Button
127. Wait until Input Pin Textbox  present
133. Verify Element Attribute Pin Textbox  with content-desc  to do action
139. Click Input Pin TextBox
145. SetText to PIN Textbox
149. delay
155. End Login Test Case
161. Wait until HamburgerButton on the Sidebar  present
165. comment
171. Verify Element HamburgerButton that have value content desc to do action
177. Click Hamburger Button
181. waitForElementPresent
185. verifyElementAttributeValue
191. Go to Mesin Kasir Menu
195. waitForElementPresent
199. verifyElementAttributeValue
205. ADD PRODUCT to shopping cart
3. Go to Mesin Kasir Menu
209. Statement - For (def index : (0..1))
1. tap
215. See shopping cart
219. tap
223. comment
227. waitForElementPresent
231. verifyElementAttributeValue
235. tap
239. waitForElementPresent
243. verifyElementAttributeValue
247. setText
251. hideKeyboard
255. waitForElementPresent
259. verifyElementAttributeValue
263. tap
267. waitForElementPresent
271. verifyElementAttributeValue
275. tap
279. waitForElementPresent
283. verifyElementAttributeValue
287. tap
291. waitForElementPresent
295. verifyElementAttributeValue
299. tap
303. waitForElementPresent
307. verifyElementAttributeValue
311. setText
315. hideKeyboard
319. waitForElementPresent
323. verifyElementAttributeValue
327. tap
331. waitForElementPresent
335. verifyElementAttributeValue
339. tap
343. waitForElementPresent
347. verifyElementAttributeValue
351. tap
355. waitForElementPresent
359. verifyElementAttributeValue
363. tap
367. waitForElementPresent
371. verifyElementAttributeValue
375. tap