1. comment
5. Statement - apkPath = apkName
9. startApplication
13. delay
21. If there is a Update TopuUp, click No, Else you can delay for waiting lazyload
25. Statement - action = new io.appium.java_client.TouchAction(driver)
29. Statement - action.longPress(550, 300).moveTo(100, 300).release().perform()
33. delay
37. Statement - action.longPress(550, 300).moveTo(100, 300).release().perform()
41. delay
45. Statement - action.longPress(550, 300).moveTo(100, 300).release().perform()
49. delay
53. Statement - action.longPress(550, 300).moveTo(100, 300).release().perform()
57. delay
61. waitForElementPresent
65. tap
69. comment
73. comment
79. Wait until Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna Textbox present
85. Verify Element Attribute Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna  with content-desc  to do action
91. SetText to Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna Textbox
97. Hide Keyboard
103. Verify Element Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna which has been you set
109. Wait until Masuk Button  present
115. Verify Element Attribute Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna  with content-desc  to do action
121. Click Masuk Button
127. Wait until Input Pin Textbox  present
133. Verify Element Attribute Pin Textbox  with content-desc  to do action
139. Click Input Pin TextBox
145. SetText to PIN Textbox
149. delay
155. End Login Test Case
161. Wait until HamburgerButton on the Sidebar  present
165. comment
171. Verify Element HamburgerButton that have value content desc to do action
177. Click Hamburger Button
181. waitForElementPresent
185. verifyElementAttributeValue
191. Go to Mesin Kasir Menu
195. waitForElementPresent
199. verifyElementAttributeValue
205. ADD PRODUCT to shopping cart
3. Go to Mesin Kasir Menu
209. Statement - For (def index : (0..1))
1. tap
215. See shopping cart
219. tap
223. comment
227. waitForElementPresent
231. verifyElementAttributeValue
235. verifyElementVisible
239. waitForElementPresent
243. verifyElementAttributeValue
247. tap
251. waitForElementPresent
255. verifyElementAttributeValue
259. tap
263. waitForElementPresent
267. verifyElementAttributeValue
271. tap
275. waitForElementPresent
279. verifyElementAttributeValue
283. setText
287. hideKeyboard
291. waitForElementPresent
295. verifyElementAttributeValue
299. setText
303. hideKeyboard
307. verifyElementText
311. waitForElementPresent
315. verifyElementAttributeValue
319. tap
323. closeApplication