1. comment
7. Call "apk" from Global Variabel
13. Start Application
19. Give delay for install "apk"
29. If there is a Update TopuUp, click No, Else you can delay for waiting lazyload
35. Function to call appium server to swipe to side
41. Call function swipe to side
45. delay
49. Statement - action.longPress(550, 300).moveTo(100, 300).release().perform()
53. delay
57. Statement - action.longPress(550, 300).moveTo(100, 300).release().perform()
61. delay
65. Statement - action.longPress(550, 300).moveTo(100, 300).release().perform()
69. delay
75. Wait until the swipe is done to do "Mulai" button
81. Tap "Mulai" Button
87. Look at Comment Input!
93. Look at Comment  Input!
99. Wait until Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna Textbox present
105. Verify Element Attribute Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna  with content-desc  to do action
111. SetText to Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna Textbox
117. Hide Keyboard
123. Verify Element Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna which has been you set
129. Wait until Masuk Button  present
135. Verify Element Attribute Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna  with content-desc  to do action
141. Click Masuk Button
147. Wait until Input Pin Textbox  present
153. Verify Element Attribute Pin Textbox  with content-desc  to do action
159. Click Input Pin TextBox
165. SetText to PIN Textbox
171. Give delay for the Server to sent your PIN
177. End Login Test Case
183. Look at Comment Input!
189. Wait until HamburgerButton on the Sidebar  present
195. Verify Element HamburgerButton that have value content desc to do action
201. Click Hamburger Button
207. Wait until Produk Button on the Sidebar  present
213. Verify Element Produk Button that have value content desc to do action
219. Click Produk Button
225. Verify Onboarding Produk screen if element is visible
231. Give delay
237. Look at Comment Input!
243. Look at Comment Input!
249. Wait until the sytem verify every element in the product board
255. Verify element "Tambah Barang" button based on content-desc
261. Tap "Tambah Barang" button
267. Look at Comment Input!
273. Wait until "Tambah Barang" button  is done to do
279. Verify element "Jumlah Stock" by Typing that has a content-desc
285. Clear Text
291. Set the count of product in "Jumlah Stock by typing" element
297. Hide Keyboard
303. Verify value that you set in "Jumlah Stock bby typing" element
309. Look at Comment Input!
315. Wait until the systems is done to verify element text
321. Verify "Nama Barang" Element that have content-desc
327. Call random string in Custom Keyword package
333. Input "Nama Barang" based on random string(Custom keyword)
339. Hide Keyboard
345. Verify if two objects are equal. (what you input is the with your output)
351. Look at Comment Input!
357. Wait until the system is done to verify "Nama Barang" output
363. Verify "SKU Produk" element that has content-desc
369. call random string in Custom Keyword package
375. Input "SKU Produk" based on the random string(Custom Keyword)
381. Hide Keyboard
387. Verify if two objects are equal. (what you input is the with your output)
393. Look at Comment Input!
399. Wait until the system is done to verify two objects are equal
405. Verify "Pilih Kategori" Element that has content-desc
411. Tap "Pilih Kategori"
415. Statement - If (com.kms.katalon.core.mobile.keyword.MobileBuiltInKeywords.verifyElementVisible(com.kms.katalon.core.testobject.ObjectRepository.findTestObject(Object Repository/Sidebar Menu/Produk/Tambah Barang/PilihKategori_Screen), G_ShortTimeOut, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE) == true)
2. tap
6. verifyElementVisible
421. Wait until before action is done
427. Verify "List Kategori Element 5th" element has content-desc
433. Tap "List Kategori Element 5th"
439. Look at Comment Input!
445. Scroll by text  to find Pilih Supplier text
451. Wait until before action is done
457. Verify "Stock Rendah"field has content-desc
463. Clear "Stock Rendah" field
469. Input your Stok Rendah in "Stock Rendah" field