1. comment
5. Statement - apkPath = apkName
9. startApplication
13. delay
21. If there is a Update TopuUp, click No, Else you can delay for waiting lazyload
25. Statement - action = new io.appium.java_client.TouchAction(driver)
29. Statement - action.longPress(550, 300).moveTo(100, 300).release().perform()
33. delay
37. Statement - action.longPress(550, 300).moveTo(100, 300).release().perform()
41. delay
45. Statement - action.longPress(550, 300).moveTo(100, 300).release().perform()
49. delay
53. Statement - action.longPress(550, 300).moveTo(100, 300).release().perform()
57. delay
61. waitForElementPresent
65. tap
69. comment
73. comment
79. Wait until Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna Textbox present
85. Verify Element Attribute Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna  with content-desc  to do action
91. SetText to Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna Textbox
97. Hide Keyboard
103. Verify Element Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna which has been you set
109. Wait until Masuk Button  present
115. Verify Element Attribute Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna  with content-desc  to do action
121. Click Masuk Button
127. Wait until Input Pin Textbox  present
133. Verify Element Attribute Pin Textbox  with content-desc  to do action
139. Click Input Pin TextBox
145. SetText to PIN Textbox
149. delay
155. End Login Test Case
161. Wait until HamburgerButton on the Sidebar  present
167. Verify Element HamburgerButton that have value content desc to do action
173. Click Hamburger Button
177. comment
181. waitForElementPresent
185. verifyElementAttributeValue
189. tap
193. waitForElementPresent
197. verifyElementAttributeValue
201. tap
205. verifyElementVisible
209. verifyElementVisible
213. verifyElementAttributeValue
217. tap
221. verifyElementVisible
225. Statement - ErMsg = com.kms.katalon.core.mobile.keyword.MobileBuiltInKeywords.getText(com.kms.katalon.core.testobject.ObjectRepository.findTestObject(Sidebar Menu/Pengeluaran/Tambah Pengeluaran/BayarViaApps/ErMsg-Akan Hadir), G_ShortTimeOut)
229. verifyEqual
233. Statement - ErMsg = com.kms.katalon.core.mobile.keyword.MobileBuiltInKeywords.getText(com.kms.katalon.core.testobject.ObjectRepository.findTestObject(Sidebar Menu/Pengeluaran/Tambah Pengeluaran/BayarViaApps/ErMsg-Rekening yang dapat dihubungkan...), G_ShortTimeOut)
237. verifyEqual
241. waitForElementPresent
245. verifyElementAttributeValue
249. tap
253. verifyElementVisible
257. delay
261. pressBack
265. verifyElementVisible
269. closeApplication