1. comment
7. Call "apk" from Global Variabel
13. Start Application
19. Give delay for install "apk"
29. If there is a Update TopuUp, click No, Else you can delay for waiting lazyload
35. Function to call appium server to swipe to side
41. Call function swipe to side
45. delay
49. Statement - action.longPress(550, 300).moveTo(100, 300).release().perform()
53. delay
57. Statement - action.longPress(550, 300).moveTo(100, 300).release().perform()
61. delay
65. Statement - action.longPress(550, 300).moveTo(100, 300).release().perform()
69. delay
75. Wait until the swipe is done to do "Mulai" button
81. Tap "Mulai" Button
87. Look at Comment Input!
93. Look at Comment  Input!
99. Wait until Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna Textbox present
105. Verify Element Attribute Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna  with content-desc  to do action
111. SetText to Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna Textbox
117. Hide Keyboard
123. Verify Element Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna which has been you set
129. Wait until Masuk Button  present
135. Verify Element Attribute Nomor HP/Nama Pengguna  with content-desc  to do action
141. Click Masuk Button
147. Wait until Input Pin Textbox  present
153. Verify Element Attribute Pin Textbox  with content-desc  to do action
159. Click Input Pin TextBox
165. SetText to PIN Textbox
171. Give delay for the Server to sent your PIN
177. End Login Test Case
183. Look at Comment Input!
189. Wait until HamburgerButton on the Sidebar  present
195. Verify Element HamburgerButton that have value content desc to do action
201. Click Hamburger Button
207. Wait until Produk Button on the Sidebar  present
213. Verify Element Produk Button that have value content desc to do action
219. Click Produk Button
225. Verify Onboarding Produk screen if element is visible
231. Give delay
235. comment
239. comment
243. delay
247. waitForElementPresent
251. verifyElementAttributeValue
257. Click Cari Produk - Parent
263. SetText in Cari Produk - Parent
267. hideKeyboard
271. waitForElementPresent
275. verifyElementAttributeValue
279. tap
1. delay